A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Catalogue FA915
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University records, Catalogue
1965-1979
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research
Rockefeller University
FA915
0.44 Cubic Feet 1 box, consisting of eleven volumes.
1 box, consisting of eleven volumes.
File Plan note
Former Classification: I 419
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be restricted from scholarly research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment.
Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be restricted from scholarly research at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/RAC Head of Reference.
Conditions Governing Access note
This collection is open for scholarly research.
Operations management; Medical research; Cell and biomolecular sciences; Life sciences; Medical sciences; Medical education; Biology -- Research; Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research; Rockefeller University
- 1965-1966 (Box 1)
- 1968-1969 (Box 1)
- 1969-1970 (Box 1)
- 1970-1971 (Box 1)
- 1971-1972 (Box 1)
- 1972-1973 (Box 1)
- 1973-1974 (Box 1)
- 1975-1976 (Box 1)
- 1976-1977 (Box 1)
- 1977-1978 (Box 1)
- 1978-1979 (Box 1)